# Levan lakobidze

(+995) 598132316 | levaniakobidze25@gmail.com | Tbilisi, Georgia

### **SUMMARY**

Dedicated web developer with three years of experience, including one year of working in the industry. I pay close attention to details, and my commitment to doing excellent work is a top priority. I'm eager to learn and grow, ready to bring innovative ideas and teamwork to any project, contributing to the success of the team.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Front-End Developer (Freelancing), CarrentalGt, November 2023-February 2024

- Led the implementation of responsive and interactive web interfaces using Next.js, ensuring seamless integration with backend systems.
- Translated design concepts into functional web pages and optimized features for performance and cross-browser compatibility.

Mentor, React.js Developer, Bitcamp, January 2023-August 2023

- Mentoring beginner web developers
- Worked extensively on Next.js projects

React Developer (Internship), Tlancer, November 2022-February 2023

- Implementing front-end tasks.
- Added new features and implemented design changes in collaboration with team members

### **SKILLS**

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React.js
- Next.is
- Context-api
- Redux-toolkit

- Linux
- Docker
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDb
- Git / Github

## **EDUCATION**

Civil engineering, Georgian technical university, Tbilisi, TB 2024

### freecodecamp

- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures
- Responsive Web Design, Legacy Responsive Web Design.

### **SOCIALS**

GitHub LinkedIn Portfolio